cmstorm.com 2018-06-29

# Cooler Master: Privacy Policy

##### Last updated: May 30, 2018

**1\. What’s in this policy?**

This policy tells you:

  * What information we might collect about you
  * How we might use that information
  * When we might use your details to contact you
  * What information of yours we might share with others
  * Your choices about the personal information you give us

**2\. What does this policy cover?**

This policy covers the services that are offered by the Cooler Master Technology Inc.

And sometimes it covers services offered by parts of our organization that operate as separate companies.

What’s not covered in this policy?

Our services sometimes link to services run by other companies, like embedded online videos such as Youtube or analytics platforms such as Google Analytics. Those companies have their own privacy and cookies policies, so remember that the information you give them will follow their rules and not ours.

We sometimes offer Cooler Master branded services to other companies, like Cooler Master YouTube page, Facebook, Twitter, Reddit and Instagram. Make sure to check their privacy policy so you know how they will use your information.

**3\. How do you protect my personal information?**

We're strongly committed to keeping your information safe. And to do this we design our services with your safety in mind. We also have dedicated teams to look after your information security and privacy.

At the same time, no service can be completely secure - if you have any concerns that your CM Fanzone account, CM Store accounts, or personal information has been put at risk, for example if someone could have found out your password, please get in touch straight away.

Where we store your information

Some companies that provide service to us run their services from different regions. Keep in mind that when you give us personal information it could be being transferred, stored or processed in a location outside the EEA.

What types of personal information does Cooler Master collect about me?

We'll give details about why we need your personal information and how we'll use it before you begin, unless it's obvious.

a. Information that you give us

We might ask for your name and contact details, your date of birth or locations, depending on what you’re doing. For example: If you apply for an online RMA service, we might ask you about your contact information.

b. Device information

Devices are lots of things like:

  * Your computer
  * Your mobile
  * Your tablet

We automatically collect some technical information from these devices and web browsers even when you’re not signed in to a Cooler Master (CM Fanzone) account. This might include:

  * IP (internet protocol) address

c. Information on your activities outside of Cooler Master when you talk about us 

Like if you’ve mentioned us in a Facebook post, we’ll collect your Facebook handle.

What if I have a CM Fanzone account?

When you register for a CM Fanzone account, or update your details or settings we ask for some personal information, like your email address and age.

We also collect information about how you use our services, like the articles you read.

What if I have a CM Store account?

When you register for a CM Store account, we’ll also collect specific information needed to deliver your order, and process your payment securely.

**4\. How long will the Cooler Master keep my personal information?**

When you give us any personal information we'll let you know how long we'll hold it for. And always stick to these principles:

  * We only hold your information for as long as we do the activities we told you about or have a valid reason to keep it
  * For our FanZone and CM Store accounts, we will keep data which allows you to have continued use of your account services until you request to close or delete your account.
  * We design our services so that we don't hold your information any longer than we have to

**5\. How can Cooler Master use my personal information?**

We have to have a valid reason to use your personal information. Sometimes we might ask your permission to do things, like when you subscribe to an email. Other times, when you'd reasonably expect us to use your personal information, we don't ask your permission, but it fits with the rights you have.

We use your information for these types of things:

a. to deliver our services and to provide you with information about them

b. to deal with your requests, complaints and enquiries.

c. to help us understand what kind of services you might use

d. to recommend things we think might interest you

e. to research and innovate

f. to contact you about various things

**6\. When will Cooler Master use my information to contact me?**

We might use your information to contact you about different things, like:

  * To update you on any changes to the Cooler Master’s policies and Terms of Use
  * To check with you about any service or activity you’ve signed up for.
  * To contact you about a creation you sent us
  * To answer you when you've contacted us, or to respond to a comment or complaint
  * To invite you to take part in surveys about the Cooler Master services, which are always voluntary
  * For marketing purposes
  * To send you notification on your device if you’ve selected them in your settings.

We'll only contact you when we need to or when you've given us permission.

We'll never contact you to ask for your CM Fanzone or CM Store account password.

**7\. Will I be contacted for marketing purposes?**

We’ll only send you marketing email if you’ve agreed to this.

You can unsubscribe anytime.

**8\. Can I delete my information?**

For CM FanZone, it is possible to  delete your account with immediate effect. However, it’s important to note:

  * We keep a record of how you've used our services, but this information can't be linked back to you
  * We also keep anything you've uploaded or commented on

For CM Store, it is possible to have your account deleted by sending a request through our store contact form. Your account deletion will be performed within 2 working days of receiving your request. It’s also important to note here that:

  * We will keep a record of how your account had used our services, and its order history.

**9\. What are my rights?**

You're in control of your personal information, you have the right to:

  * To ask us to correct information that's wrong, to delete it or to request that we only use it for certain purposes
  * To change your mind, and ask us to stop using your information. For example, unsubscribing from any marketing emails

**10\. How does Cooler Master use cookies and similar tracking?**

a. What are cookies and tracking technologies?

Cookies are bits of data which are stored in your computer or mobile when you visit a website or app.

b. Why do we use cookies and other tracking?

  * To remember information about you.
  * To keep you signed in, even on different devices.
  * To help us understand how people are using our service, so we can make them better
  * To find out if our emails have been read and if you find them useful

A few things on our websites wouldn't work without some cookies. Tech people call these "strictly necessary cookies". They're always on when you visit us.

But we want to use others like functional, performance and advertising cookies to make your experience more enjoyable. We'll only use them if you've agreed. You can always change your mind.

Bear in mind there are some other cookies out there from other companies. These "third-party cookies" might track how you use different websites, including ours. For example, you might get a social media company's cookie when you see the option to share something. You can turn them off, but not through us.

c. How long do cookies last?

Some are erased when you close the browser on your website or app. Others stay longer, sometimes forever, and are saved onto your device so they're there when you come back.

d. How do I control my cookies and tracking?

You are always able to delete the cookies in the security settings of your browser.

Stopping all cookies might mean you can't access some Cooler Master services, or that some of them might not work properly for you.

For more information, please refer to [Cookie Policy](http://www.coolermaster.com/company/agreement/cookie-policy/).

**11\. How will I find out about changes to this policy?**  
We update this policy sometimes. If we make important changes, like how we use your personal information, we'll let you know. It might be a notice or an email.

**12\. What’s different for kids?**

a. We might ask you to tell us your age  
For example: When you want to get a CM Fanzone account or join our online/offline campaign

b. Sometimes we'll ask to get your parent or guardian's consent  
You'll see a notification. We might also ask for some details from them,

c. Sometimes we'll tell your parents about your activities  
For example, if you're under 13 and your parent has asked to see every creation you upload, we'll share it with them before it goes public.

d. What we do when you post, upload or share a creation  
When you share your creation with us we'll try to tell you exactly what we're going to do with it.

e. You're in control of how we use cookies and tracking

Cookies are bits of data that are stored on your device. Some things on our websites wouldn't be able to work without these cookies. So they're always on when you visit us.

We use cookies and tracking to make things easier for you, like remembering where you got to in a game or what emoji you selected.

You can switch off some cookies and similar tracking technologies. Or your parent or guardian can do this if you're under 13.

f. You've got privacy rights, the same as adults, so get to know what they are  
You can:

  * ask us what personal information we hold about you
  * ask us to correct or delete your personal information
  * tell us to stop using your personal information

If you're 13 or older, you can do this yourself, but not always.  
Sometimes we'll be asking for your parent or guardian to do that.  
If you're under 13 your parent or guardian probably has to do it for you.

**13\. How can I contact Cooler Master?**

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect, you can request to see this information and have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, please email **data-protection@coolermaster.com.tw**
